(Q1) ⭐ come in to see us —— 来见我们；来面谈｜agency representative —— 机构代表；代理机构工作人员｜one of... —— ……之一
⭐ speak on the phone —— 通电话｜didn't we? —— 对吧？（反意疑问）
⭐ send in —— 提交；寄送｜CV (curriculum vitae) —— 简历｜have a careful look at... —— 仔细查看……｜be suitable for... —— 适合……
⭐ based in... —— 位于……｜look for... —— 寻找；招聘｜administrative assistant —— 行政助理
⭐ what sort of... —— 什么类型的……
[Q1答案句] ⭐ be called... —— 名为……｜design and make... —— 设计并制造……｜furniture —— 家具（不可数）
⭐ know much about... —— 对……了解很多｜sound interesting —— 听起来有趣
(Q2) ⭐ as I said —— 正如我说的｜look at your experience —— 查看你的经历｜look as if... —— 看起来似乎……｜fit the requirements —— 符合要求｜quite a few —— 不少
⭐ it appears... —— 看起来……｜data entry —— 数据录入
[Q2答案句] ⭐ one skill they want —— 他们需要的一项技能｜appoint someone —— 任命/录用某人｜attend meetings —— 参加会议｜take notes —— 做笔记；记录
⭐ I've done that before —— 我以前做过
(Q3) ⭐ be able to —— 能够……｜cope with —— 处理；应付｜general admin —— 日常行政工作
[Q3答案句] ⭐ filing —— 文件归档｜keep records —— 保存记录｜and so on —— 等等｜manage the diary —— 管理日程安排
⭐ something they want —— 他们需要的东西｜suggest doing sth —— 建议做某事｜add something to your CV —— 把某项内容加入简历
⭐ mention —— 提及
(Q4) ⭐ as far as...go —— 就……而言｜requirements —— 要求｜particularly mention —— 特别提到｜spreadsheet —— 电子表格
⭐ interpersonal skills —— 人际交往能力｜check something with someone —— 向某人核实某事｜reference —— 推荐人；证明人
[Q4答案句] ⭐ take care with details —— 注意细节｜look at your CV —— 查看你的简历｜probably alright —— 应该没问题
(Q5) ⭐ special experience —— 特殊经验
⭐ experience of... —— ……方面的经验｜teleconferencing —— 电话会议；远程会议
⭐ three years' experience —— 三年经验
[Q5答案句] ⭐ in fact —— 事实上｜at least —— 至少｜might interest you —— 可能让你感兴趣
⭐ The only thing is... —— 唯一的问题是……｜commute —— 通勤｜a long commute —— 长距离通勤
(Q6) ⭐ position —— 职位｜suit someone better —— 更适合某人｜as far as location goes —— 就地点而言｜warehouse assistant —— 仓库助理
⭐ a lot closer —— 近很多
⭐ work in a warehouse —— 在仓库工作
[Q6答案句] ⭐ responsibilities —— 职责｜manage stock —— 管理库存｜deliveries —— 配送
⭐ keep track of... —— 跟踪；掌握情况｜be good with numbers —— 擅长数字
(Q7) ⭐ requirement —— 要求｜computer literate —— 具备电脑技能的
⭐ organisational skills —— 组织能力｜well organised —— 有条理的
[Q7答案句+确认]
⭐ go together —— 相互关联
(Q8) ⭐ the usual stuff —— 常见要求｜communicate orally and in writing —— 进行口头和书面沟通
⭐ one of the things I enjoyed most —— 我最喜欢的事情之一｜be part of a team —— 成为团队的一部分
⭐ essential for... —— 对……非常重要
[Q8答案句（代词指代）] ⭐ be used to doing sth —— 习惯做某事
(Q9) ⭐ what sorts of... —— 什么类型的……｜deal with... —— 处理……
⭐ mostly —— 主要地｜equipment —— 设备（不可数）
[Q9答案句] ⭐ move heavy things —— 搬重物
⭐ have the training —— 接受过培训
(Q10) ⭐ as far as experience goes —— 就经验而言｜have a licence —— 有驾照
⭐ cope with traffic —— 应付交通
[Q10答案句] ⭐ customer service —— 客户服务｜you're OK there —— 你这方面没问题
⭐ What about...? —— ……怎么样？｜a bit more about... —— 更多关于……的信息